Guide to the Vassar College Facilities Operations Records, 1800s-2021 (bulk 1908-1999)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series I. Administrative Files, 1879-2011
  - [College Center] Division 10 - Specialties, 1974 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] 10-15 - Metal Toilet Partitions, 1974 (Box 40)
  - [College Center] 0-50 - Lockers, 1973 (Box 40)
  - [College Center] 10-80 - Toilet Accessories, 1973 (Box 40)
  - [College Center] 11-90 - Kitchenette, 1973 (Box 40)
  - [College Center] Division II - Equipment, 1974-1975 (Box 40)
  - [College Center] 11-40 - Food Services Equipment, 1974 (Box 40)
  - [College Center] Div. 13 - Special Construction [Music Practice Rooms], 1974 (Box 40)
  - [College Center] Div. 14 - Conveying Systems, 1974 (Box 40)
  - [College Center] Plumbing, 1973 (Box 40)
  - [College Center] Sprinklers, 1973-1975 (Box 40)
  - [College Center] Electrical, 1973-1974; (2 folders) (Box 40)
  - [College Center] Fire Alarm, 1973 (Box 40)
  - [College Center] College Center HVAC, 1973-1974; (4 folders) (Box 40)
  - [College Center] Phone Pad, 1973 (Box 40)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Helen D. Lockwood Library and Alteration to Thompson Library Vassar College Project Manual [Official Office Copy], 1974 (Box 40)
  - Charts and Graphs [square footage of buildings and capacity], 1969 (Box 40)
  - Regional College Representatives, 1970 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence [Higher Facilities Planning], 1969-1970 (Box 40)
  - Space Utilization Manual, 1970 (Box 40)
  - Questions, 1969 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewers and Drains - Laundry and Service Building to Creek, 1940 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Proposed A.C. to Ely Aula from Swift, 1945 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Proposed A.C. to Ely Aula From E/. Manhole East of Ely, 1945 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - A.C. to Room #22 Rockefeller Hall, 1946 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Lower Farmhouse (Weibeke) for Electric Lighting, 1945 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Electric Service to Cow Barns and Rombout Measurements taken February 13, 1929 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - F.A. and C.B. Cables (2) from Nursery School to Palmer House, 1945 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Distributing Board in Main Building Basement (Looking North), undated (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Proposed Electric Manhole By-Pass around Manhole #9, 1944 (Box 40)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Electric - Kenyon Hall Cost Estimates, undated (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Electric By Pass Around Steam Manhole North West of Chapel Bill for concrete duct, 3 sets of Joint Material and Labor, 1933 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - 1928 Electrical Construction Costs (Box 40)
  - [Wimpfheimer Nursery School] Electric - Nursery School Panel Circuits, 1928 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Replacement of #6 Weatherproof Wire with #4 From Main Line at Horse Barn to Rombout Bill, 1929 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Replacement of #6 Weatherproof Wire with #4 from Main Line, Raymond Ave., To Pole Rear of Mr. Arthur’s House Bill, 1929 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Location of Electric Manhole, uncovered Jan. 24, 1933 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Main Building Street Lights, 1931 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Service to Professor Treadwell’s House, Nov. 1931 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Sketches for Proposed One Line Diagram Map of Electric Service, Feb. 19, 1931 (Box 40)
  - [Taylor Hall] Electric - Taylor Hall Lighting Service Repairs Work Order #325, 1929 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Distances Between Manhole Centers Taken Mar. 4, 1929 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Street Lamps 1928 Construction (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Service to Mr. Arthur’s House Measurements Taken February 13, 1929 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Beginning of Electric Service to Farm - Measurements Taken Feb. 13, 1929 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Electric Service to Taylor Hall, 1929 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Dimmer Layout at Vassar College, 1932 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - 1929 Electrical Construction to Mr. Arthur’s House from Main Line on Raymond Ave. (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - New Electric Bypass Around Steam Manhole North of Chapel, 1933 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Service to Kenyon Hall Sketch Showing Location of Starting Point (Stake) of Survey, 1933 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Angle for Electric Ducts to Nursery School, 1927 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - New Electric Service to Warden’s House, 1933 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Manholes 1-4, 1939 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Telecommunications - Telephone Lines, Vassar College, 1939 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Replacement of #6 Weatherproof Wire with #2 from Main Line at Horse Barn to Cow Barn Bill, 1929 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Replacing Cable Between Steam Manholes No. 7 and 8, Raymond Ave. June 16, 1948 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Proposed New Duct, Manholes and Cable from Steam Manhole Just East of Chapel to Alumnae House, 1945 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Skinner Hall and Physics Lab Street Lamps, 1931 (Box 40)
  - Building Surveys, 1928-1949 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewer - Skinner Hall, 1931 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewer - Wing Farm, 1969 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewer - Sewer Line Check, January 1950 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewer - President’s House, 1938 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewer - Sewer for Vivarium, 1944 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewer - Playhouse, North of Kenyon Hall, 1938 (Box 40)
  - Work Order 817 - 2” H.P. Line to South Side Academic Buildings Construction, 1934 (Box 40)
  - Grounds - College Avenue Area, 1927 (Box 40)
  - Grounds - Walks and Roads West of Main Building, 1932 (Box 40)
  - Grounds - Section South of Vassar Lake and South East Avenue and Raymond Avenue and Denney’s Property, 1938-1967 (Box 40)
  - [Avery Hall] Heat - Avery Hall - Details for Reconstruction of Heating System. 1934 (Box 40)
  - Grounds - Skinner Hall Area, 1931 (Box 40)
  - [Library - Van Ingen] Van Ingen Hall - Standing Radiation, 1937 (Box 40)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Kenyon Hall Heating Survey, 1944 (Box 40)
  - [Ely Hall] Ely Hall Radiation, 1942 Jul 29 (Box 40)
  - Greenhouse Radiation, 1932 (Box 40)
  - Total Number of Square Feet Radiation in Buildings Heated By Vassar College [Voided October 20 1932] (Box 40)
  - Josselyn House - Heat, undated (Box 40)
  - [Skinner Hall] Heat To Skinner, undated (Box 40)
  - [President's House] New Heating Duct to President’s House 1931 Construction Estimate (Box 40)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Proposed A.C., 1951 Mar 2 (Box 40)
  - [Taylor Hall] Electric - Measurements Taken After Duct Construction, Taylor Hall, 1936 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Location of Electric Manhole East of Chemistry Lab, 1927 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric Manhole Drawings, 1927-1944 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Details of Heating Tunnel at Physics Lab, 1928 Apr (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Heating Branch to Greenhouse, 1930 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Manhole Plan, undated (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Library Heating Indirect, 1937 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Heating Service Estimates, 1926 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Location of Hot Wells in Relation to Boiler House, undated (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Heating Reports for Skinner Hall and Greenhouse, 1930 May 7 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Heat to Gym, 1930 May 9 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Heating Reports, 1926-1934 (Box 40)
  - Square Foot Radiation Survey, 1932 Oct 19 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewer From Good Fellowship Clubhouse, 1937 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Heat - Kenyon Hall, 1933 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Street Lights Sketches, 1927-1947 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Heat - Heating Duct to Vassar Brothers Lab and New England Building 1934 Construction (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Heat - Services and Piping Raymond and College Avenue Houses, 1926-1928 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric and Telephone - Baldwin House (New Infirmary), 1939 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric and Telephone - College Avenue Houses, 1944 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] A.C. to Blodgett, Nov. 1938, also quotations on M.G. Set (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Replacing Electrical Service to Alumnae House from Manhole North West of Williams Hall, 1941 Construction Work Order 412 - A (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Kenyon Hall, 1933-1949 (Box 40)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] A.C. to Kenyon Hall from Manchester Road, Summer, 1949 (Box 40)
  - Estimate-Proposed Street Lamps, Gray Wing Farm, 1937 (Box 40)
  - Equipment Journal for Easley (Blodgett) Library, undated (Box 40)
  - Equipment - Coal Larrie and Chute, Boiler House, 1946 (Box 40)
  - Equipment - Metal and Woodworking Machinery Survey, 1941 Apr (Box 41)
  - Equipment - Lectern from Room 35 Rockefeller, undated (Box 41)
  - Equipment - Coal Conveyor and Crane, 1927-1930 (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] General - Services to the Dean’s House, 1931 (Box 41)
  - Equipment - Stoker Drive (Steam) and Motor, 1927 (Box 41)
  - Equipment - Boiler Feed Pump, 1927 (Box 41)
  - Equipment - Euthenics, undated (Box 41)
  - Equipment - Vassar College Track Dimensions, undated (Box 41)
  - Equipment - Stoker Speeds and Gearing Boilers 1,2 and 5, 1927-1933 (Box 41)
  - Equipment - Flat Ironer, 1932 (Box 41)
  - Equipment - Preliminary Sketches for Blodgett Hall Vertical Sliding Blackboard Auditorium, undated (Box 41)
  - Equipment - Ventilating Fan, Taylor Hall, Basement, 1936 Sep 23 (Box 41)
  - Equipment - Moulton Journal Case, Chemistry Lab Library, 1935 Apr 22 (Box 41)
  - Equipment - Motor, undated (Box 41)
  - Equipment - Sketches of Nose and Throat Treatment Equipment as is installed at Dr. Krieger’s Office, 1934 (Box 41)
  - Equipment - Goulds Pump-B.B. Layout, 1933 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Water Mains 1934 Reconstruction, Raymond Ave. and College Ave. and Campus. Work Order 813 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - Street Lights Estimates etc., 1931-1938 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Farm Greenhouse Rombout Skinner, 1927-1947 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Water Line Construction, 1927 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - 6” Universal Pipe and Hydrant, undated (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - 300,000 Gallon Storage Tank Piping and New Fire Pump 1937 Construction (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - College Avenue Section, 1927 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - 6” Water Service to Baldwin 1939 Construction (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Golf Course, Water Tank, Tabard, Hockey Fields, 1930-1949 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Kenyon Hall Area, Water Piping, 1927-1949 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Blodgett, Cushing, Nursery School, 1938 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Kendrick House, 1926 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Nursery School and Wing Farm Area - Water Piping, 1933-1938 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Chemistry, Physics, Avery Open Air Theatre, 1933 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - South Campus, 1926-1955 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - College Avenue, 6” Water Main, Ferrell House-Welch House, undated (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - West Section of Campus, 1926-1947 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Water Meter List, 1932 Jan 21 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - [Proposed Water Main Connection Between Main Building and Boiler House to Service Buildings], 1947 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Coal Bunker, 1936, 1950 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - North Hall Cold Water Piping Layout in Building, 1941 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Location of New Hydrants, 1927 Aug 15 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Laundry Water Consumption, 1940 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - 1926 Construction Universal Pipe and Fittings Laid, Work Order 43 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Water Meters to be Installed, 1928 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Position of Fire Plugs in Front of Proposed House, 1926 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Old Gas Holder East of Infirmary Change Order, 1937 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Location of Hydrant in Rear of Avery Hall, 1926 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Water Meters Near Pump House, undated (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water Lines or Fire Lines, undated (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Water Lines and Consumption Reports, 1927-1946 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Gamon Meter Company Water Meter Quote, 1928 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Town of Poughkeepsie Water System Notes, 1943 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water - Water Meter Installation and Survey, 1928 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Wing Farm Surveys, 1930 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Vassar Lake Survey, Fall of 1942 and other Information (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Skinner Hall, 1941 (Box 41)
  - Fulton Ave. Property - John Ogden, undated (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewers and Drains - Ely Hall, 1926-1948 (Box 41)
  - [Baldwin Hall] Sewers and Drains - Baldwin House, 1939 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewers and Drains - College Avenue Sewer, North Side, Work Order 628-A, May 5, 1944-1945 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewers and Drains - Raymond, Davison, Strong, Lathrop, Jewett, Josselyn, 1926-1949 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewers and Drains - Cushing House and Vicinity to 1932, 1927-1932 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewers and Drains - New Garage (East of Boiler House), Boiler House, Pump House, Sewer Pump House, P.P. Superintendent’s House, 1927-1950 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewers and Drains - Palmer House, 1938, 1945 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewers and Drains - Raymond Avenue Sewer and Tie to Campus and Locations of Some Faculty Houses, 1926-1942 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewers and Drains - Library, 1949-1950 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewers and Drains - Main Building, 1927-1938 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewers and Drains - Blodgett and Nursery School, 1928-1949 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewers - Kenyon Hall, 1933-1935 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Drains - Kenyon Hall and Cemetery Drains, 1927-1944 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Rough Estimate - Sewer From Pierce House, 156 College Ave. to Manhole North of #160, 1945 (Box 41)
  - Sunset Lake, South End Dam Bridge, 1952 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Alumnae House Road and Walk, 1931 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Raymond and College Avenue Surveys, Survey around Dean’s House, 1931 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Alumnae House Road, 1931, 1943 (Box 41)
  - [Chapel] Buildings - Chapel, 1927-1954 (Box 41)
  - [Alumnae House] Buildings - Alumnae House, 1951 (Box 41)
  - Buildings - General, 1938-1942 (Box 41)
  - [Library - Van Ingen] Library - Van Ingen, 1939 (Box 41)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Buildings - Blodgett Hall, 1941-1949 (Box 41)
  - [Baldwin Hall] Buildings - Baldwin House (New Infirmary), 1939 (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] 149 College Avenue - Booth House, 1945 (Box 41)
  - Buildings - Coal Pockets, Cottage Street, 1943-1945 (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] 145 College Avenue, 1948 (Box 41)
  - Eleanor Conservatory (Outside Dimensions) January 4, 1933 (Box 41)
  - [Student Housing] Co- op. Housing Unit - Property Services etc., 1949 (Box 41)
  - [Cushing House] Cushing House, 1951-1952 (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] 81 Raymond Ave - 'D' Cottage, 1942-1944 (Box 41)
  - Doctor’s Garage, 1942 Feb 2 (Box 41)
  - [Main Building] Vassar College (Main Building), (Student Living Area Only), undated (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] Ellis House, 1940 Jul 23 (Box 41)
  - [Davison House] Buildings - Davison, 1949-1957 (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] Rombout House (Flagler House) - Attic, 1946 (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] 141 College Avenue - Gow House, 1947-1948 (Box 41)
  - Greenhouses, 1927-1941 (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] Hill House - For Fire Escape, Raymond Ave, 1946 (Box 41)
  - [Jewett House] Jewett Hall (North), 1942-1957 (Box 41)
  - [Ely Hall] Buildings - Ely- Aula Set-ups (Sketches), 1941-1943 (Box 41)
  - [Ely Hall] Buildings - Ely Hall General, 1933-1944 (Box 41)
  - [Ely Hall] Buildings - Ely Hall Geology, 1934-1936 (Box 41)
  - [Vassar College Farm] Buildings - Farm, Cow Barn, East Poultry House, 1932 (Box 41)
  - Fire Pump House - Building Sketches, 1937 (Box 41)
  - Garage - East of Boiler House Sketches of the Existing Old Coal Bunkers etc., undated (Box 41)
  - Josselyn House, 1948 (Box 41)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Kenyon Hall, 1941 (Box 41)
  - [Vassar College Farm] Buildings - Hughes Farm House - Sketches of Floor Plans, 1940-1942 (Box 41)
  - Ice House Later Garage (Garage Destroyed by Fire Night of Nov. 24 1929) (Box 41)
  - [Kendrick House] Kendrick House, 1948 (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] Low Cost Housing Project - Vlackte Area (Faculty Projects), 1941 (Box 41)
  - [Main Building] [Buildings] - Main Building Estimates etc., 1947-1950 (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] 147 College Avenue - Lyman House, 2nd Floor Proposed Apartment, 1943-1950 (Box 41)
  - [Main Building] [Buildings - Main Building Floor Plan Sketches], 1926-1937 (Box 41)
  - [Metcalf House] Metcalf, Proposed Addition to the Kitchen, 1939 (Box 41)
  - [Wimpfheimer Nursery School] [Buildings] - Nursery School, undated (Box 41)
  - [New England Building] [Buildings] - New England Building, Proposed Additions to the Present Balcony, 1955 (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] Palmer House (Wing Farm House), 1931-1939 (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] Palmer Apartments (proposed), April 1939 (Wing Farm House), 1939-1954 (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] Warden’s House (Pratt House) - Detail, undated (Box 41)
  - President’s House, 1935-1946 (Box 41)
  - [Powerhouse Theater] Buildings - Power House Sketches of Power House and Coal Bunkers - used in connection with Unit No. 5 1932 Construction, 1931-1935 (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] Raymond and College Avenue Houses (House Sizes), 1932 (Box 41)
  - [Raymond House] Buildings - Raymond Baths Etc., 1941-1954 (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] Riley House, floor plans, Raymond Ave, 1954 Jan 25 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Buildings - Sewer Pump House [Dimensions], 1942 (Box 41)
  - Sheet Iron Storage Building (For Furniture), Proposed, 1935 (Box 41)
  - [Skinner Hall] Buildings - Skinner Hall, 1929-1932 (Box 41)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Buildings - Students Building, 1939-1960 (Box 41)
  - [Faculty Housing] 69 Raymond Ave - Tonks House, 1954 (Box 41)
  - [Library - Van Ingen] Buildings - Van Ingen, 1948-1950 (Box 41)
  - [Williams House] Williams House, 1948-1951 (Box 41)
  - Buildings - Paul E. Zehe Estate, 100 Overlook Road, New Rochelle, N.Y. Sketches of Floor Layout and Inventory of Furnishings, Taken Jan. 11-12, 1944 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Gas - Gas Lines to Davison and Prof. Fite and Washborn Houses, 1927 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Gas - Gas Service to Nursery School and Cushing Hall, 1946 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Gas - Location of Central Hudson Gas and Electric, 1932-1943 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Gas - Plans and Surveys, 1938-1943 (Box 41)
  - Outdoor Theatre Stage, 1961 May (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Gas - Gas System-1939 and 1940 Construction, 1940-1943 (Box 41)
  - Ecological Garden Survey for Skinner Hall Site, Also Along Easterly Side of Raymond Ave., 1929 Nov (Box 41)
  - Josselyn House - Rear Wing - West Side, 1954 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Transit Stations and Flagstone Walks, 1939-1946 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Baldwin House Area, 1939 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Blodgett, Cushing, Kenyon, Nursery School Area, 1926-1938 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Chapel Gate, 1931 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - College Ave. Property, 1948 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Flower Circle and Surrounding Area Showing Location of Trees and Walks, 1952 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Original Land Purchases By M. Vassar [Transcribed], undated (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Wing Farm Surveys, 1939 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Hockey Fields and Tennis Courts, 1927-1932 (Box 41)
  - Dr. MacCracken - Hornyback, Oct. 1942, 1926 (Box 41)
  - Lisburne Grange, 1946-1947 (Box 41)
  - Quadrangle Elevations, 1951 May 28 (Box 41)
  - Vassar College Farm Road and Pond Measurements, 1959 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Ice Hockey Rink Northeast of Kenyon, 1936 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - Skinner Hall Bridge, 1944-1946 (Box 41)
  - Grounds - New Concrete Sidewalk West of Main Building 1941 Construction, 1941-1945 (Box 41)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Heating and Electrical Ducts, 1931-1949 (Box 41)
  - [Baldwin Hall] Heat - Baldwin House (New Infirmary), 1939 (Box 41)
  - [Studio Arts Building] Cost Estimates and Budgets, 1991-1993 (Box 42)
  - [Studio Arts Building] Bidding Summary and Backup, 1992 (Box 42)
  - [Studio Arts Building] Construction Contract and Misc., 1992 (Box 42)
  - [Studio Arts Building] Construction Contracts, Owner/Contractor, 1992 (Box 42)
  - [Studio Arts Building] Constituents Fees, 1993 (Box 42)
  - [Studio Arts Building] Expenses, 1994 (Box 42)
  - [Studio Arts Building] Supplemental Instruction, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - [Studio Arts Building] Requests for Information, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - [Studio Arts Building] Schedules, 1993 (Box 42)
  - [Studio Arts Building] Field Reports, 1992 (Box 42)
  - [Studio Arts Building] Technical Reports, 1993 (Box 42)
  - [Studio Arts Building] Soils Testing Report, 1992 (Box 42)
  - [Studio Arts Building] Change Order Requests and Estimates, 1993 (Box 42)
  - [Studio Arts Building] FF and E Invoicing, 1993 (Box 42)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Seeley Mudd, 1984-1985 (Box 42)
  - Pull Sheet Wiring Code, undated (Box 42)
  - [College Center] College Center Specifications, 1973 (Box 42)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Mudd Chemistry Building Specifications, 1982; (2 folders) (Box 42)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Budgets / Estimates / Value Engineering, 1996 (Box 42)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Correspondence File, 1994 (Box 42)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Blodgett Construction Estimates, 1994-1996 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Blodgett Hall Renovation - Schedule, 1996 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Blodgett Hall Renovation - Pre Design Phase, undated (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Anthropology NSF National Science Foundation Grant, undated (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Master plan, 1993-1994 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Anthropology NSF National Science Foundation Grant Phase I Design, 1993-1996 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Blodgett NSF National Science Foundation Grant (1994), 1994-1995 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Program, 1993 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] General, 1994-1995 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] C.III. Architect Selection Phase, 1990-1994 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] RFP, 1993-1994 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] A/E Proposals, 1994 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] A/E Contract, 1993 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] C.IV - Design Phase, 1994 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Draft Schematic Design Report, 1994 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Anthropology Project, 1997 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Ancillary Space Needs, 1996-1997 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Blodgett Hall Correspondence and Acoustic Testing, 1996 (Box 43)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Blodgett Moves, 1998 (Box 43)